

LARS SMET

GAME DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm Lars, a 21-year-old from Belgium. I am a passionate game development student at Digita Arts and Entertainment. While studying, I fell in love with game design, I even took an extra course to improve my skills. Creativity is my strongest attribute and I love coming up with new ideas for the industry.

SKILLS

- -Creativity
- -Open-minded
- -Problem-solving
- -Teamwork and communication
- -Leadership
- -Working under pressure

CONTACT

Phone: 04 68 11 23 72

Mail: lars.smet2002@gmail.com

Address: Kortenbosstraat 72 Massemen

Belgium

Portfolio: larssmet.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Vice-Chair at Howest Esports

January 2023-present

I was one of the pioneers who started Howest Esports. Currently, I am vice-chairperson. We promote Esports at our school, organize events, streams and manage teams.

Chess Teacher at Koninklijke Wetterse Vrijpion

September 2019-present

I teach chess to children between 6 and 12 years old at my hometown's chess club.

EDUCATION

Economy and scienceSint-Gertrudis College

2014-2020

Game Development

Howest - Digital Arts And Entertainment

2020 - present

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & SOFTWARE

C#

C++

Unity

Unreal

Perforce

Github

LANGUAGES

Dutch, native English, fluent French, basics

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

Gaming
Going out with friends
Chess
Dancing